showmypc.com 2008-12-16

# ShowMyPC.com - Web Conferencing, Instant Desktop Sharing, Access Remote PC Free, Online Meetings

---  
  
## ShowMyPC Privacy Policy

April 15, 2007

At ShowMyPC we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use ShowMyPC's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. 

### Scope

This notice offers highlights of the full ShowMyPC Privacy Policy, which describes in detail the privacy practices that apply to ShowMyPC's products, services and websites worldwide (collectively, ShowMyPC's "services").   
\- At this point we do not ask for any personal information, including, email, login, or registration of any kind.   
\- ShowMyPC collects personal information only when users voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other ShowMyPC services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.   
\- ShowMyPC uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use ShowMyPC services in order to improve the quality of our services.   
\- ShowMyPC's servers automatically record usual information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

### Uses

\- We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising (so far none).   
\- We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve ShowMyPC technologies and services.   
\- We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of ShowMyPC.   
\- When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
\- We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.   
\- ShowMyPC processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. 

### Your Choices

\- We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible.   
\- You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result.   
\- We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

### More Information

For more information about our privacy practices, or if you have additional questions, please contact support@showmypc.com or go to Feedback.
